users = {"Monty": {"password": "helloworld", "victories": 100}}

questions = {1: {"question": "Friends star Lisa Kudrow was originally cast in the sitcom Frasier.",
                 "answer": True},
             2: {"question": "If you’re born between May 1st and 20th, then you’re a Gemini.",
                 "answer": False},
             3: {"question": "There are over 2,500 stars on the Hollywood Walk of Fame.",
                 "answer": True},
             4: {"question": "Fruit flies were the first living creatures sent into space.",
                 "answer": True},
             5: {"question": "Cyclones spin in a clockwise direction in the southern hemisphere.",
                 "answer": True},
             6: {"question": "Goldfish only have a memory of three seconds.",
                 "answer": False},
             7: {"question": "Dolly Parton is the godmother of Miley Cyrus.",
                 "answer": True},
             8: {"question": "Roger Federer has won the most Wimbledon titles of any player.",
                 "answer": False},
             9: {"question": "An octopus has five hearts.",
                 "answer": False},
             10: {"question": "Brazil is the only country in the Americas to have the official language of Portuguese.",
                 "answer": True},
             11: {"question": "The Channel Tunnel is the longest rail tunnel in the world.",
                 "answer": False},
             12: {"question": "Darth Vader famously says the line “Luke, I am your father” in The Empire Strikes Back.",
                 "answer": False},

             }
